#### Contact

dfgd08555@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/roei-redler (LinkedIn) shreddler.com/roei/ (Portfolio)

### Top Skills

Microsoft Excel Analytical Skills Self Learning

### Languages

Hebrew (Native or Bilingual) English (Professional Working)

# Roei Redler

Shift Manager at Israel Ministry of Defense Central

## Summary

Student at third year undergraduate degree in Business Administration specializing in information systems.

professional in Microsoft Office applications and especially in Excel.

I really like and connect to the world of data and believe it is a very powerful tool.

Also, Always responds positively to challenges and tries to find technological solutions.

## Experience

Israeli Ministry of Defense 3 years 2 months

Shift Manager

December 2020 - Present (1 year 1 month)

Central, Israel

Shift Manager and Deputy Director of the Ministry of Defense Service Center Management of 20 employees.

The role requires:

- Interpersonal communication and high emotional intelligence.
- Create reports and track data.
- Process testing and analysis capability, flexibility of thought and function.
- High ability to motivate employees.
- Distinguishing between the main thing and the bland.
- Systemic and business vision.
- Computer operations and systems including Office, knowledge management systems, BI systems, CRM systems, quality control systems and listening management.
- Dealing with stress situations and dealing with several factors at the same time.

-Transfer training to employees.

Call Center Customer Service Representative November 2018 - December 2020 (2 years 2 months) Central, Israel

Customer Service Representative at the Ministry of Defense Call Center The role requires:

- Dealing with stress situations and dealing with several factors at the same time.
- Quick learning
- Ecstations on financial matters
- Organization and order
- Operations of computer software such as: Office, CRM.
- Ability to work independently.
- High human relations.
- Remote user support.

Israeli Air Force Aircraft Interceptor August 2015 - March 2018 (2 years 8 months) Fighter in the IDF Air Defense Unit

## Education

Ono Academic College

student, BA in Business Administration in Information Systems  $\cdot$  (2019 - 2022)

Premilitary Academy "Elisha" graduate, Bible/Biblical Studies · (2014 - 2015)

Amit Kfar Ganim Yeshiva graduate, A high school diploma · (2008 - 2014)